Chris Watters: Operation Phantom Sight
is coming to Rainbow 6 Siege.
The Phantom in this title is Nokk, an attacker
who uses her gadget to muffle her footsteps,
keep herself out of the spotlight,
and creep everyone right out.
The Sight is Warden, a sharp dressed defender
whose glasses allow him to resist or recover from flashes
and to see more clearly when things get smoky.
We'll give you the details on these two new operators
and show you around the newly renovated Cafe Dostoyevsky,
no reservation necessary.
First, let's meet the guy in the tie, Warden.
Fresh off a stint with the United States Secret Service,
Warden is a dapper defender who accessorizes
with his Glance smart glasses and a snazzy statement watch.
When things start popping off, Warden switches
glasses on to accomplish all of the following.
Number one, make himself immune to flashes.
Number two, remove any flash he is currently affected by.
Number three, give him clearer sight through smoke.
And number four, add some high tech panache to his I
just killed you scream.
You can manually deactivate the glasses
or wait until they run out of juice and need to recharge.
Either way, there is a fixed cool down
before you can activate them again.
But there's no limit to how many times
you can use them in a match.
With his glasses active, Warden is a strong counter
against any smoke and flash party
that the attackers try to throw.
If Blitz gets frisky or Ying lights
up a whole mess of Candelas, Warden
will be having none of it.
Even Glaz will have to think twice
about setting up behind his precious smoke screen,
though he still has an edge on Warden
with his bigger scope and thermal detection.
Note that the smoke filtering feature on Warden's glasses
is less effective if he's moving, so picking smart angles
and repositioning quickly are vital to making
the most of his gadget.
And while his glasses are active,
you'll need to watch out for the gadget
disabling and gadget detecting powers of Thatcher and IQ.
But as a high armor, low speed operator wielding either an MPX
submachine gun or an M590A1 shotgun,
Warden makes for a strong anchor and he looks good doing it.
Hailing from a different quadrant of the fashion galaxy,
we have Nook.
This attacker from Denmark's Jaeger Corps
may have an eye-catchingly eerie get up
but she would actually prefer it if you didn't notice her
at all.
So when her hell presence reduction gadget is active,
you won't hear her footsteps and you won't see any sign of her
on camera feeds.
It's a little spooky.
And with all the different potential camera
feeds available to defenders these days,
Nokk's ability to hide from them all is all the more alarming.
Her gadget runs off a recharging meter like Warden's glasses
but, unlike Warden's glasses, there's no required cool
down so Nook can turn her gadget on and off and on again
whenever she has the juice to run it,
giving her more tactical flexibility.
And activating her gadget doesn't require
her to change weapons, so she can
continue wielding her primary, an FMG9 submachine gun or 612SD
shotgun, or her secondary, a Five-SeveN USG
pistol or a D50 pistol with an equippable suppressor.
This makes Nokk a formidable flanking and fragging threat
though, like any operator, she has her limitations.
Nokk's gadget will glitch and be visible on camera
feeds if she performs basically any action except moving
at a normal speed or slower, crouching
and moving, or reloading or swapping weapons.
You can also keep an eye out for environmental clues,
like breach debris moving of its own accord.
Or you could take a more proactive approach
and throw down some barbed wire razor wire.
Nokk will glitch while passing through it.
If you really want to make things tricky for Nokk,
take Lesion and his goo mines.
She'll glitch when she steps on one,
glitch every time she takes damage,
and glitch while she pulls out the needle.
Aside from the glitch, the only other camera interference
that will let you know Nokk is nearby
is this wave form effect that appears
when using Mozzie's hacked drones or Echo's Yokai.
Every other camera will have a hard time seeing,
and your ears will have a hard time
hearing, this medium speed, medium armor attacker.
Team Nokk up with a roamer hunting operator
or take her on a sneaky flanking route
and you've got a powerful new way
to unsettle the defending team.
The map you've been seeing here may look familiar.
It's Cafe Dostoyevsky or Cafe to its friends.
The seige team has renovated this lovely three story
gathering spot, creating new bomb sites,
making old sites more viable, and generally sprucing things
up for more balanced encounters.
For example, enter through the new reception area and you'll
find a stairwell has moved, opening up
new possibilities for opening up the reading room.
The kitchen area has been extensively remodeled and given
a festive touch.
And there's even been some light roof work.
The shiny new cafe map will replace the old cafe map
for free when Operation Phantom Sight launches.
The two new operators, Warden and Nokk,
will be available at launch for Year Four pass owners
and unlockable for all players seven days later
by using Renown or R6 credits.
For more on Rainbow Six Siege, subscribe to this channel
and visit us at news.Ubisoft.com.
[MUSIC PLAYING]